downloader.my 2012-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Downloader.MY Premium Download |

This privacy policy may be changed at any time.

Agreement relating to confidentiality. 

#### IP Addresses Recording

Our servers can detect the IP Address of Users connection through the Internet. These IP addresses are recorded by our servers for internal use only (registration on the site, optimal use of downloads, etc.).

#### Email Addresses Recording

Our server stores the email addresses of Users during registration for internal purposes only. Under no circumstances, we will rent, sell, or send personal data's to third parties.

#### Use of Cookies

We use cookies for Users convenience by saving the connection to the site (thus avoiding unnecessary reconnections). We do not use tracking methods.

#### Payment Informations

All payments made on our website are managed by outside firms. Payments are secure and encrypted, in any case these companies can not save Users banking information.

#### Exeptional Disclosure of Personal Data

We may be required to disclose Users personal data in order to protect our legal rights or where disclosure of Users personal data's are required of us by the judicial authorities only when legal procedures are followed.

#### Advertisments

The advertisements on our website are offered by other companies. They can use information about Users visits in order to target content which will potentially interest Users (Name, mailing address, etc. are excluded from these data). 

#### Datalogging

Files links that Users download are not stored on our server. All the files are stream remotely by our server from the filehosting direct to users pc.
